blogs4us.com 2015-05-22

# Website Privacy Policy | Lamatsultrim Khandro

What data will we acquire?

We acquire data from you when you register within our site, make a purchase, subscribe with our newsletter, reply to a survey or Complete a out form.

While ordering or registering within our site, as suitable, you may be requested to enter in your: title or e-mail address. You might, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, a third party vendor, utilizes cookies to serve advertisements on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users primarily based on their visit on your sites and other sites on the World-wide-web. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and written content network privacy policy..

How do we use your details?

Any of the data we acquire from you may be used in one of the following methods:

  * To personalize your knowledge  
(your data helps us to better reply to your individual needs)
  * To boost our web site  
(we continually try to boost our web site offerings primarily based on the data and feedback we receive from you)
  * To boost customer service  
(your data helps us to more successfully reply to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To process transactions
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site function
  * To send periodic email messages

Your data, no matter whether community or private, won’t be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other organization for any motive in any respect, without having your consent, other than for the express goal of offering the purchased product or service requested.

The email address you provide may be used to send you data, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

How do we guard your data?

We implement a selection of security measures to sustain the safety of your private data when you enter, submit, or access your private data.

We offer the use of a safe hosting server. All supplied delicate/credit data is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Database to be only accessed by those authorized with particular access rights to our systems, and are required to keep the data confidential.

After a purchase, your private data (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be saved on our servers.

Do we store cookies?

Yes (Cookies are smaller files that a site or its service supplier transfers to your personal computers hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the web sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and seize and remember certain data

We use cookies to help us remember and process the goods in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for long term prospects, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer greater site encounters and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service suppliers to assist us in better comprehending our site visitors. These service providers are not allowed to use the data collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and boost our company.

If you prefer, you can select to have your computer system alert you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can decide on to turn off all cookies via your browser configurations. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our solutions may not operate properly. Nonetheless, you can still place orders by contacting customer|consumer|client} service.

Do we disclose any data to outside parties?

We do not promote, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside events your personally identifiable data. This does not include trustworthy third parties who assist us in operating our web site, running our company, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this data confidential. We may also launch your data when we believe release is suitable to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or shield ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable customer data may be supplied to other parties for advertising, promoting, or other uses.

Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may consist of or offer third party products or services on our web site. These third party web sites have separate and self-sufficient privacy policies. Thus, we have no duty or liability for the content and activities of these linked web sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these web sites.

Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not acquire any data from anyone under 13 years of age. Our web site, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

Online Privacy Policy Only

This on-line privacy policy is applicable only to data collected through our web site and not to data collected offline.

Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions segment establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our web site at /terms

Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our site privacy policy.

modifications to our Privacy Policy

If we choose to alter our privacy policy, we will publish those changes on this page.

This policy is powered by Free Privacy Policy and Rhino Support. Compare Rhino Support to Zen desk and save!

Be Sociable, Share!

  *
